Guide to the Bill Bytsura ACT UP Photography Collection 1981-2012 (Bulk 1989-1997) MSS.313
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Demonstrations
  - [November 2, 1992 Mark Fisher Political Funeral], December 31, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Stand Up Harlem- Negatives 1993, April 5, 1993; August 19, 1993; August 24, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - [Housing Works], May 24, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - June 9, 1993 [AIDS Conference Berlin], June 9, 1993; June 15, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - [Shut Down US HIV Concentration Camp], September 30, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - [Broken Promise Clinton], December 4, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Negatives 1994, August 23, 1994; February 5, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Stand Up Harlem- Group Shot, February 5, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - [In the Tradition of Stonewall], August 24, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Negatives 1995, April 10, 1995; May 6, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - August 24, 1993 [Party], September 1, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Pataki-Albany Demonstration- Negatives 1996-1999, June 7, 1996; July 1, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - [Governer Pataki Protest], June 7, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Act Up Week: Tom Duane Outweek March 1997 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Hate Crime Press Conference, March 30, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Wall Street Demonstration, March 30, 1997 (Box 16, Drawer 17)
  - [Queer Rights Now], January 11, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - June 4, 1998 [Political Funeral Steve Michael], June 9, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - [Staging HIV Surveillance, Contact Sheet], August 24, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - [Matthew Shepard Protest], January 29, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - [undated and miscellaneous] (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - [Tim Bailey Act Up Funeral, Washington DC], July 1, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Series III: Press, Promotion, and Adminstrative Files
  Series III: Press, Promotion, and Adminstrative Files includes articles and magazines featuring Bytsura's work, as well as promotional materials and objects such as t-shirts, a hat and buttons, and a few administrative items such as budgets.
  - Action No. 36, December 1995 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Act Up Invoices, 1993-1997 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Aids Entertainment Weekly [Act Up Paris], June 6, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Aids Treatment News Issue No. 269, April 18, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Beautiful Thing: A New Play [Postcard], 1999 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - The Birth and Evolution of a New Social Movement Organization: Act Up, Phillip B. Lott University of West Florida, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Body Positive: December 1993; March 1994; May 1994; August 1994, January 18, 1994; 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Body Positive: October 1994; November 1994; February 1995; March 1995; May 1995; July 1995, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Bravo Pour Votre Combat [Act Up Paris], June 1995 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Grant/Gallery, 1991-1998; undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Project, November 4, 1992; June 1, 1993; February 9, 1994; February 10, 1994; September 19, 1994; November 1, 1994; april 12, 1997; July 15, 1997; [undated] (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - [Exhibition Comments and Signature Book], undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - HX- The Totally Biased Politically Incorrect Party Paper: Issue no. 407, June 25, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - HX- The Totally Biased Politically Incorrect Party Paper: Issue No. 402 and Issue No. 415, May 21, 1999; August 20, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - HX- The Totally Biased Politically Incorrect Party Paper: Issue No. 416, August 27, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Mandate, July 1992 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - National Gallery of Australia, December 13, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Newsweek: Lesbians "What if a cure is far off?", June 21, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - New York Magazine [Article with Bytsura Photo], June 15, 1998; June 22, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - New York Magazine: Act Up Twenty-Five Years On, April 2, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Next Magazine vol. 8 Issue 24, December 22, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - NYQ no. 7 United in Anger Quba Libre!, December 8, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - [Phone Number Lists], February 3, 1992, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Proposal: Action in front of the Argentine Consulate, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - PWA Newsline Issue 77, June 1992 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Rome Gay News no. 35-29, February 1992 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Shout! Magazine vol. 1 Issue 2, December 6, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - SIDA Ahora # 11, Summer 1992 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - [Stand Up Harlem Administrative Papers], 1993, undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Travel Tickets, May 7, 1993; May 1997; April 1997; June 1997; [undated] (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - United in Anger [Budget and Miscellaneous], November 5, 1993; January 18, 1994; [undated] (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Welcome to NY: Stonewall 25 [Newspaper], June 1994 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Yell Zine, undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Series IV: Ephemera
  Series IV: Ephemera includes a hat, t-shirts, stickers, pins and postcards.
  - Subseries A: T-Shirts and Hat
    - Act Up New York [Green], undated (Box 19, Object ID: 313.2.0001)
    - Act Up New York [Red], undated (Box 19, Object ID: 313.2.0002)
    - Act Up Miami [Black and White], undated (Box 19, Object ID: 313.2.0003)
    - Act Up [Sleeveless; Black and White], undated (Box 19, Object ID: 313.2.0004)
    - Act Up New York [Purple], undated (Box 19, Object ID: 313.2.0005)
    - Act Up New York [Sleeveless; Red], undated (Box 19, Object ID: 313.2.0006)
    - Act Up [Sleeveless; Black and White], undated (Box 19, Object ID: 313.2.0007)
    - Act Up Atlanta [Multi-colored], undated (Box 19, Object ID: 313.2.0008)
    - Act Up New York [Sleeveless; Green], undated (Box 19, Object ID: 313.2.0009)
    - Ignorance= Fear, Keith Harring Design [Yellow], undated (Box 19, Object ID: 313.2.0010)
    - Art For Activism Limited Edition 1Act Up, undated (Box 19, Object ID: 313.2.0011)
    - Be Here for the Cure: San Francisco Aids Foundation, undated (Box 19, Object 313.2.0012)
    - Red Hot and Blue: A benefit for Aids Research and Relief, undated (Box 19, Object ID: 313.2.0013)
    - Aidsgate, undated (Box 19, Object ID: 313.2.0014)
    - Culture Alone Can't: Condoms Can, undated (Box 19, Object 313.2.0015)
    - Life Liberty and the Pursuit of Happiness, undated (Box 19, Object ID: 313.2.0016)
    - Read My Lips, undated (Box 19, Object ID: 313.2.0017)
    - Read My Lips [darker], undated (Box 19, Object ID: 313.2.0018)
    - Men Use Condoms or Beat It, undated (Box 19, Object ID: 313.2.0019)
    - Les Femmes Aussi Meurent Du Sida, undated (Box 19, Object ID: 313.2.0020)
    - Silence = Death, undated (Box 19, Object ID: 313.2.0021)
    - Silence = Death [Sleeveless], undated (Box 20, Object ID: 313.2.0022)
    - Blind Silence = Death Action = Life, undated (Box 20, Object ID: 313.2.0023)
    - The Parliament Confirms that Danish Efforts Against Aids Will Continue to be Based on Autonomy: Berlin 1993, undated (Box 20, Object 313.2.0024)
    - PositHIV Frauen Power, undated (Box 20, Object ID: 313.2.0025)
    - Intercambio de Agujas Limpias [Sida], undated (Box 20, Object 313.2.0026)
    - Solo se vive una vez [Sida], undated (Box 20, Object ID: 313.2.0027)
    - Servicios Medicos Nuestro Derecho, undated (Box 20, Object ID: 313.2.0028)
    - Australian Federation of AIDS Organisations Berlin AIDS Conference 1993 (Box 20, Object ID: 313.2.0029)
    - Yo Tengo Sida, undated (Box 20, Object ID: 313.2.0030)
    - Aids Sida No Neen Non Nao Nej Oxi Nein, undated (Box 20, Object 313.2.0031)
    - Ignorance is your enemy: Act Up Paris, undated (Box 20, Object ID: 313.2.0032)
    - Act Up Hat, undated (Box 20, Object ID: 313.2.0033)
  - Subseries B: Buttons, Stickers, and Postcards
    - Compact Disc: Blind: Silence = Death; Action = Life, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Buttons, Stickers, and Postcards, undated (Box 24)
- OVERSIZE Series I: Portraits
  - Agosto, Moises, December 10, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Bailey, Tim, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Bennett, Anthony, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Bennett, Mona, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Blotcher, Jay, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Brand, Charles, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Contini, Alan, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Corbin, Marc [Miami], undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Cunningham, Tom, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - d'Adesky, Anne-Christine, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - DiPaulo, Joey, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Episalla, Joy, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Ewing, Larry Reece, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Farber, Robert, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Fell, Blair, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Fons, Christopher, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Garanca, Frank Ruth, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Garcia, Robert, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Gekeler, Corinna, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Getty, Jeff, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Geyer, Hans-Jorg, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Goldberg, Ron, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Graham, Jeff; Stinner, Peter [Atlanta], undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Gray, Natasha, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Greenough, Dene; Martin, Floyd, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Groom, Neil, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Hammerstaedt, Bettina [Berlin], undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Haneef, Balil, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Haner, Hal, undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Hensler, Rebecca, undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Hilferty, Robert, undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Hulse, Jimmy, undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Kramer, Larry, undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Lopez, Louis; Sawyer, Eric, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Magenti, Marie, undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Marks, Joe, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Mazyck, Joyce, undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - McKean, Aldyn, undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Mendez, Juan, undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Meyhdert [Amsterdam], undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Nicholson-Earle, Brent, undated (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Northrop, Anne, undated (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Oscar [Ft. Lauderdale], undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Otter, Kathy, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Palmer, Marvin, undated (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Payan, Ilka, undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Phillips, Suzanne, undated (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Pierre, undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Provenzano, Jim, undated (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Robinson, Dave, undated (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Rollerina, undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - [Sara and Nadine], undated (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Schillow, Manfred, undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Seggerman, Maryann, undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Sigman, Carl, undated (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Signorile, Michelangelo, undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Simon, Gloria, undated (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Sissyfag, Luke, undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - St. Angelo, Madrid, undated (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Stodgell, Terry and Desiree [Father Daughter San Francisco], undated (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Teigeler, David [Amsterdam], undated (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Tigger, undated (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Turkott, Jim, undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Turner, Wayne and Steve, undated (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - [Unidentified Portraits], undated (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Vasquez, Robert, undated (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Vellay, Cleevus, undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Vitale, Bruno, undated (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Vlasveld, Lizet, undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Voelker, John, undated (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Wagner, Jim, undated (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Wieder, Harry, undated (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Wiggins, Michael, undated (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Williams, Cheryl [Atlanta], undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Wolfe, Maxine, undated (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - OVERSIZE Series II: Demonstrations
      - [Bush Demonstration], undated (Box 21, Folder 47)
      - Unidentified Demonstrations, undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Zwickler, Phil, undated (Box 21, Folder 46)
- OVERSIZE Series III: Promotion and Press
  - The All-Greed Journal [Mock Newspaper]; City Aids Actions, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - LGNY- Lesbian and Gay New York: Issue 100, February 25, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - LISP- A Collection of Anecdotes and True Stories, Fully Illustrated, Summer 1995 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - [Lyrics and Letterhead], undated (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - The New York Times Magazine, November 28, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 49)
- OVERSIZE Series IV: Ephemera
  - Act Up International Posters, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - 'Crack Kills' Poster, undated (Box 22, Folder 37)